{
    "categories": [],
    "description": "Guess the type of these famous animals.",
    "difficulty": -1,
    "questions": [{
        "answer": "Mouse",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Mickey"
    }, {
        "answer": "Cat",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Garfield"
    }, {
        "answer": "Clownfish",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Nemo"
    }, {
        "answer": "Duck",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Daffy"
    }, {
        "answer": "Elephant",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Dumbo"
    }, {
        "answer": "Lion",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Mufasa"
    }, {
        "answer": "Dog",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Lassie"
    }, {
        "answer": "Reindeer",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Rudolph"
    }, {
        "answer": "Chipmunk",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Alvin"
    }, {
        "answer": "Frog",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Kermit"
    }, {
        "answer": "Dolphin",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Flipper"
    }, {
        "answer": "Bear",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Yogi"
    }, {
        "answer": "Spider",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Charlotte"
    }, {
        "answer": "Donkey",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Eeyore"
    }, {
        "answer": "Killer Whale",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Shamu"
    }, {
        "answer": "Penguin",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Pingu"
    }, {
        "answer": "Skunk",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Pepé Le Pew"
    }, {
        "answer": "Turtle",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Yertle"
    }, {
        "answer": "Owl",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Hedwig"
    }, {
        "answer": "Moose",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Bullwinkle"
    }, {
        "answer": "Rat",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Splinter"
    }, {
        "answer": "Horse",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Shadowfax"
    }, {
        "answer": "Monkey",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Marcel"
    }, {
        "answer": "Gorilla",
        "category": "Famous Animals Quiz",
        "question": "Koko"
    }],
    "quizLength": 24,
    "title": "Famous Animals Quiz",
    "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/famous-animals-quiz.php"
}